[
    {
        "question": "The Niagara Falls empties in which Great Lake?",
        "answer": "Lake Ontario"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Peace Garden State`?",
        "answer": "North Dakota"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to the University of Oregon?",
        "answer": "Eugene"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Silicon Valley is located in what California valley?",
        "answer": "Santa Clara Valley"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country administers Greenland?",
        "answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Normandy?",
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What soup is likely to be on the menu in Poland or Russia?",
        "answer": "Borscht"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Syria?",
        "answer": "Damascus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What body of water does the Danube River flow into?",
        "answer": "The Black Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the warmest continent?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Evergreen State`?",
        "answer": "Washington"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Golden Gate Bridge is located in what city?",
        "answer": "San Francisco"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Old Dominion` state?",
        "answer": "Virginia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river was dammed to create the International Amistad Reservoir?",
        "answer": "Rio Grande River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zion National Park is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "Utah"
    },
    {
        "question": "Texas City is located at the mouth of what bay?",
        "answer": "Galveston Bay"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the easternmost state in the contiguous US?",
        "answer": "Maine"
    },
    {
        "question": "Honshu is the largest island of which country?",
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest Japanese island?",
        "answer": "Honshu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the Federated States of Micronesia?",
        "answer": "Palikir"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ankara is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which continent would you find the Lena River?",
        "answer": "Asia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which river is dammed by the Hoover Dam?",
        "answer": "Colorado River"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the Canadian province of Alberta?",
        "answer": "Edmonton"
    },
    {
        "question": "Edmonton is the capital of which Canadian province?",
        "answer": "Alberta"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which continent would you find the Amazon river?",
        "answer": "South America"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two countries share land borders with Tunisia?",
        "answer": "Algeria and Libya"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Guatemala?",
        "answer": "Guatemala City"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Guatemala to the north?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Guatemala to the west?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Guatemala declare its independence from Spain?",
        "answer": "1821"
    },
    {
        "question": "Oil wrestling is the national sport of which country?",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do most tourists call the Vieux Carre?",
        "answer": "The French Quarter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to the University of Haiti?",
        "answer": "Port-au-Prince"
    },
    {
        "question": "James Bay forms the southern end of what larger bay?",
        "answer": "Hudson Bay"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island in Manila Bay was the site of a famous 1942 siege?",
        "answer": "Corregidor"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what bay would you find the Andaman and Nicobar islands?",
        "answer": "The Bay of Bengal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What bay is actually the United States` largest tidal estuary?",
        "answer": "Chesapeake Bay"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Mauritania and Guinea-Bissau?",
        "answer": "Senegal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Kazakhstan and Iran?",
        "answer": "Turkmenistan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country proclaimed the birth of its billionth citizen in 2000?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country`s cuisine includes the dish called `bibimbap`?",
        "answer": "South Korea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ladin is primarily spoken in which area of the world?",
        "answer": "Northern Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city was known as and almost permanently named `Batmania`?",
        "answer": "Melbourne, Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country set a new Guinness World Record for steepest street in 2019?",
        "answer": "Wales"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has the largest territorial claim in Antarctica?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Greece is part of which peninsula?",
        "answer": "Balkan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country`s coat of arms features a double-tailed lion?",
        "answer": "Czech Republic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What causes the gory-looking red tint of Antarctica`s Blood Falls?",
        "answer": "Iron"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Chicago`s main international airport?",
        "answer": "O`Hare"
    }
]